Jon Dyson

Full Stack Developer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self motivated and adaptive junior full stack developer, with five years of non-professional developer experience. Spent several years working for the US Army in a high intensity, intellectually demanding, small team environment as liaison and cultural expert. Recently graduated from the RefactorU, full stack immersion learning program, with a passion for code and solving problems through technology.

Willing and able to relocate.

EDUCATION

RefactorU, CO— Full Stack Immersion Course, 2016

Graduated from the RefactorU immersion learning program focused on MEAN stack development.

UConn, CT— Bachelor's Degree (BGS), 2010

Graduated with a concentration in Sociology and a minor in economics from The University of Connecticut.

Special Operations Center of Excellence, NC - CivilAffairs Operator, 2008

Graduated from the US Army's Special Warfare Center & School in the top 5% of the class (Commandant's List)

EXPERIENCE

Lotus Import Group – *Owner/Operator*, 2014 – 16

Created a small portfolio of online businesses focused on the manufacture, importation, and direct sales of a variety of consumer goods.

US Army - Civil Affairs Operator, 2008 - 16

Liaison between the US military and foreign civilian or intergovernmental interests. Civil Affairs Operators deploy in small teams and function autonomously as cultural experts to facilitate cooperation even in the most hostile environments.

International Financial Group - Underwriting, 2011-14

Responsible for providing a business risk assessment and rating for commercial general liability policies in the excess and surplus lines market. Policy risk exposure ranged from 2M to 10M aggregate.

JonDyson.com

hello@jondyson.com linkedin.com/in/jon-dyson github.com/DysonJ 860.309.5343

SKILLS

Technical

Javascript: 5 years **Angular**: < 1 year Node.js: < 1 year Express.js : < 1 year MongoDB: <1 year **iQuery**: 5 years

CSS: 5 years

Materialize: < 1 year **Bootstrap**: < 1year mySQL: 3 years msAccess: 2 years **HTML**: 5 years **ColdFusion**: 5 years

Professional Development Toastmasters: 1 Year

refactor (I)

AWARDS

Army Commendation Medal Awarded for rapid assimilation and cultural understanding in an austere environment.

Commandant's List Graduated from the Army's Special Warfare Center in the top 5% of the class.



CLEARANCE

DoD Security Clearance: Secret



Combat Veteran Operation **Enduring Freedom**





